# Teresa Lee | teresalee1231@gmail.com | 206.466.9755

### **BACKGROUND**

Recent university graduate with 4 years of experience coding in Java, Python, and C++. Experienced in working in group settings in a short amount of time. Looking for front end, back end, or full stack development roles. Has a willingness to grow and improve.

# **EDUCATION**

## **B.S. Computer Science**

University of Washington – Seattle, WA September 2019 – June 2023

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Software Developer | Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research - Seattle WA | 06/14/2021 - 09/14/2021

- Worked remotely under Michael Wu's Group in a 13 week time period.
- Assisted in the development of an R package that finds the correlation between balances of bacteria to survival outcome.
- Worked with classified microbiome bacteria data while maintaining data integrity and privacy.

### **PROIECTS**

Slimes 'n' Boxes | CSE 481d Games Capstone | 01/03/2023 - 03/09/2023

- Developed a game from scratch within 10 weeks using GDScript in the Godot game engine.
- Lead designer within a team of 5 people.
- Posted on social media and advertised the game .

## Final Project | CSE 442 Data Visualization | 11/07/2022 - 12/05/2022

- Used d3 to create interactive visualizations from Pokemon data.
- Helped design the website that these visualizations are showcased in.
- Integrated the techniques and tools aout data visualization I have learned in class.

# Cat Vs Dog Classification Kaggle Competition | CSE 455 Final Project | 02/22/2022 - 03/04/2022

- Trained on pre-existing image classification models to produce a convolutional neural network to classify images in a Kaggle Competition dataset.
- Assisted with the implementation of the model using PyTorch.
- Trained model from scratch using DarkNet.
- Trained model using transfer learning using ResNet18 and ResNet 18 SWSL.

#### OTHER EXPERIENCES

TRIO Student Associate | UW OMA&D TRIO SSS - Seattle WA | 02/06/2022 - 06/03/2022

- Designed flyers and posters for UW OMA&D TRIO SSS using Canva.
- Posted on social media to promote these events.

# Fundraising Chair | Phi Sigma Rho Sorority - Mu Chapter | 03/24/2021 - 06/03/2022

- Raised over \$700 for the Leukemia and Lymphoma Society.
- Organized and led fundraising events.
- Designed flyers and posted using Canva.
- Demonstrated leadership skills by working with a small group and discussing ideas.

# Admissions Agent | Space Needle - Seattle WA | Seasonal (06/18/2019 - 09/14/2019, 12/22/2019 - 01/02/2020)

- Worked in a fast paced environment providing information to the guests.
- Handled rapid high-volume transactions efficiently.
- Handled high amounts of tourist activity.